education2020.com 2011-10-06

# Untitled Page

**EDUCATION 2020's Privacy Policy**

EDUCATION 2020 (E2020, Inc.), is committed to protecting you and your family's privacy when you visit any of our family of web sites, or use our electronic services, such as product registration or technical support. EDUCATION 2020 does not require anyone to register or share personal information to visit most of our web sites. However, many of our sites and online products require registration to access content or other privileges provided. We do not knowingly collect and keep any of your personal information unless you volunteer it. In addition, we do not knowingly collect and keep personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. Please review the information below to familiarize yourself with our policies on web site privacy. By visiting any EDUCATION 2020 sites, you hereby agree to all the terms set forth within this Privacy Policy and listed in the Terms of Use section. 

**A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS:**   
EDUCATION 2020 adheres to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. Parents can help by spending time online with your children and monitoring your children's online use. Please help us protect your child's privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on this site or any other, or within any software registration process, without your permission.

**Does EDUCATION 2020 collect any personal information about me if I'm 13 or older?**  
EDUCATION 2020 doesn't require anyone to share any personal information about them in order to visit our web sites. However, many of our sites contain special sections and privileges for registered members. We do not collect any personal information from you unless it is provided voluntarily, for example: when you sign a guest book, register for contests, downloads, or free demos, complete our online customer surveys, send online greeting cards, purchase products, etc. Visitors to our sites must be 18 years or older with a valid credit card to purchase products. The personal information we may ask for includes first and last name, mailing address, phone number, and an email address (in addition we may collect credit card information and mailing and/or shipping address information if you are purchasing products from one of our sites). See below for how we use this information. 

**Does EDUCATION 2020 collect any personal information about anyone under 13?**  
EDUCATION 2020 courseware is not intended for children under 13.

If we determine a child under 13 sends a request to us, we keep their email address for long enough to respond to them. EDUCATION 2020 deletes this information from our system after we answer their question. 

**What does EDUCATION 2020 do with the information we collect? Does EDUCATION 2020 share information about me with others?**  
We use the personal information we collect for the purposes indicated at the time you provide such information. For instance, if you register in a contest, we will use the registration information to notify contest winners; if you purchase a product, we will use the information to fulfill the order; if you send an online greeting card, we will use the information to deliver the greeting to the provided recipient; etc. Only with consent at the time we ask for information, we might also email or mail you to provide you with information on upcoming EDUCATIN news and products, web site updates, updates on your order, and promotions. With your additional consent, we may also share information with third parties so that they can inform you and your family about their products, which might be of interest to you. EDUCATION 2020 never knowingly promotes directly to children under the age of 18. In addition, we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, and/or in cooperation with law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Except for maintenance and security reasons, we never knowingly share personal information that we receive from children under 13 with other companies. If you prefer, we will remove your name from the list we provide to outside companies. To do so, please email us at info@education 2020.com and use the subject line "REMOVE." In special circumstances, EDUCATION 2020 may give other companies access to our information database, but only if necessary for database or server maintenance, security, or other similar services. In addition, EDUCATION 2020 may employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending email, supplementing information or removing repetitive or erroneous information from customer lists and providing customer service. These entities have access to this information to perform these functions on behalf of EDUCATION 2020 only and may not use it for any other purpose. If we do provide access, we require those other companies to sign confidentiality agreements promising to keep secret any information they see. If EDUCATION 2020 believes that anyone's behavior on any of our sites may damage us, our sites, or anyone else, we may disclose the relevant personal information in order to prevent harm. In that case, we might try to identify the wrongdoer, contact them, or bring legal action against them. We may also disclose personal information if we believe that the disclosure is required by law. In the event that any of the assets relating to EDUCATION 2020 are transferred or sold to another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to the acquiring entity consistent with the terms of such agreement. 

**How do I change my contact and information usage preferences?**  
If, at any time, you want to stop receiving such updates and product information from EDUCATION 2020 or our affiliates, contact us to unsubscribe. It is recommended that you use the links at the bottom of the email you last received for removal from the email list.

Otherwise if you are receiving educator communications, contact us at info@riverdeep.net. Please type "REMOVE" in the subject line of the email.

We often have messages for our customers scheduled several weeks in advance, so unsubscribe requests can take up to three to four weeks to process through our system. Thank you for your patience.

**How does EDUCATION 2020 use cookies and other similar tracking mechanisms?**  
Cookies  
A "cookie" is a small file that we save on your computer's hard drive which contains non-personal information. These cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited; they allow you to personalize your pages; and they help you to participate in some activities or events on the site and optimize your shopping experience at our sites. We also use cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our sites, which of our web pages they visit, and how long they stay there. If you are visiting any of our shopping sites cookies keep track of items in your shopping cart and wish list. This information helps us figure out which of our web features are highly successful and which sites might need improvement. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but allow you to disable them.

Session IDs  
We use "Session IDs" to also allow EDUCATION 2020 to identify a particular user across multiple web page requests. This Session ID is maintained within your cookie file, where possible. If cookies are not enabled, or if the user's internet browser program does not support cookies then EDUCATION 2020 will place the Session ID in the requested web page. This allows the end user to avoid having to continually re-enter certain information such as account name and password for every web page request. This Session ID "expires" whenever the user closes their internet browser.

Web Site Tracking Reporting  
Many of our web pages also contain special electronic images (called a "single-pixel gif" or "gifs") that allow us to gather only non-personally identifiable traffic statistics and other aggregate information about visitors to our sites. We use this technology to collect and accumulate anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the experience of people visiting our web sites and, along with other information you provide, customize your future visits and improve our web sites. For example, we capture data on the type of browser used, operating system software (e.g. Windows 95 vs. 98 or Macintosh), cookie preferences (whether the user has them turned on or off), and search engine keywords (what key words did a visitor use to get to our site). We also record number of visits, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages within the EDUCATION 2020 sites. Please keep in mind that none of this information is personally identifiable and that we only distribute this information to internal staff at EDUCATION 2020 and to partners that have signed confidentiality agreements with us. Any information that we do share with partners reflects overall web site or Internet usage trends, not individual.

Log Data  
For administrative purposes, we collect IP addresses, which is the automatic number assigned to your computer when you surf the web, as well as operating system, browser, URL clickstream to, through and from our sites, reference site domain name as well as log time and date every time you visit our sites. This data is used to maximize the performance and efficiency of our sites. While the cookie may store first name or user name in the cookie it does not collect any personally identifiable or on-line contact information like a full name and address, so you and your family remain anonymous.

Email Tracking  
We also include a small image in most emails that we send to subscribers. As above, this allows us to gather only non-personally identifiable traffic statistics and other aggregate information about our email audience. These images notify special computers when you open an email and if you clicked on a link within the email. This helps us measure the effectiveness of our newsletters and other emails so that we can make sure we're providing you with the information and content in which you are most interested. In addition, some advertising networks that serve ads on our web sites or within our emails may use similar images or other technology within their banner advertisements to track traffic statistics. Naturally, once you leave our web sites or emails by clicking on one of these advertisements, EDUCATION 2020 does not have control over and is not responsible for the advertising networks or other third parties and the data they collect.

Subscription Product Data Tracking  
EDUCATION 2020 offers products available through its various sites on a subscription basis. Use of these subscription services shall constitute your consent to the terms of this privacy policy. To facilitate these subscription products we may collect and maintain certain information associated with your subscription. This information includes, but is not limited to, your subscription account I.D., records of your access to the subscription service, start and end date of your subscription as well as any other usage information that may be necessary to provide a well-maintained service to all our subscribers.

External links and framed Web pages  
Throughout our web site we include links to other web sites. Our privacy policy does not apply to these external links. The privacy policy of the third party web site governs the information collection and usage on such third party site. We urge parents and teachers to learn more about protecting children on the Internet by visiting the following sites:

U.S. Department of Education's Parents' Guide to the Internet   
SafeKids.com 

**Does EDUCATION 2020 ever collect information without consent?**  
Except in the circumstances described above, EDUCATION 2020 does not collect information passively through cookies or other tracking mechanisms. Cookies DON'T contain any personal information about a specific user. We don't use cookies or other non-consensual methods to capture personally identifiable information, except for certain activities like treasure hunts, which we discussed above. EDUCATION 2020 doesn't use cookies for direct marketing or promotional purposes. Cookies are not used to collect information specifically about you or your family for sharing with third parties. 

**What if the site uses banner ads?**  
Ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider. The ad service provider may place or utilize their own unique cookie on your browser, and may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our sites, such as the number of times you have viewed the ad. EDUCATION 2020 is not responsible for the collection of these cookies and is not responsible for the actions of the ad service providers. 

We may modify our policy from time to time. When this happens we will notify you of the new policy by posting it on our sites. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information we have about you. Please check our site frequently to see any recent changes.

**EDUCATION 2020 Online Curriculum Product Privacy Policy**

This Online Curriculum Product Privacy Policy applies to the online practices of EDUCATION 2020., A Limited Liability Company, and its affiliates only.

EDUCATION 2020's privacy policy applies to EDUCATION 2020's online curriculum based products including Virtual Classroom, Virtual Tutor, @Home, International and Professional Development solutions. The EDUCATION 2020 Online Curriculum solutions on require the disclosure of personally identifiable information.

**Student Accounts**

All student accounts for EDUCATION 2020 Virtual Classroom solutions must be created by the student's teacher. EDUCATION 2020 will assign the student account id during the registration process, which is typically some combination of the student's first name and some letters of the last name or numbers. The proposed name will not be the actual student's name. _Passwords are assigned by the teacher and can be reset by teacher or school administrator.

Teachers must obtain consent on behalf of the child's parents in order to register any student under the age of 13 for any EDUCATION 2020 Virtual Classroom solutions.

**Registration**

Teachers register their students for Virtual Classroom solutions by providing a student name, password, grade. Address and student specific information is optional and not required.

For additional information regarding registration, student information and privacy policy guidelines, contact us at:

EDUCATION 2020™  
7303 E. Earll Dr., Suite 200 Scottsdale, Arizona 85251  
877.2020.EDU / 877.202.0338 tel.  
480.423.0213 fax
